http://www.animelosangeles.org/policies/#non-harassment

Non-Harassment Policy
Harassment of any kind, including physical assault, battery, deliberate intimidation, stalking, or unwelcome physical attentions, will not be tolerated. If people tell you “no” or to leave them alone, your business with them is done. If you continue to attempt to have contact with those people, you may be removed from the premises.
The following general rule supersedes all others and may be invoked at any time:
Any action or behavior that causes significant interference with convention operations, excessive discomfort to other attendees, or adversely affects the convention’s relationship with its guests, its venues or the public is strictly forbidden and may result in permanent suspension of membership
Props Policy
We recognize that costume-related props are sometimes an important part of the costume experience, so our convention has the following props policy for costume-related props in place:
ALL prop weapons must be non-working and peace-bonded (see below).
No functioning projectile weapons includes water pistols, silly-string guns, and ping-pong pistols. Bladed weapons must be cased or sheathed at all times.
No “live-steel”, aluminum, or other metallic bladed weapons are allowed to be without casing or sheathing, even if the blade has been dulled.
There will be absolutely no play-acting with props indoors
Explosives or chemicals of any kind including, but not limited to, smoke powder, sparklers, and fireworks, are not permitted at the con Do not bring anything that would annoy another attendee
Peace-bonding is the act of making it clear that your weapon cannot be used (either by a brightly colored tie, or trigger lock) and that your intentions are peaceful. In order to display a costume related prop weapon on your costume, your prop weapon must be peace-bonded; to do so, it must be brought to the Convention Operations (“Ops”) room which is located on the first floor of the Ontario Convention Center. Do not presume that the peacebonding from another or a previous convention will do. Items producing light or sound must be checked with ConOps for decisions about peace-bonding.
These rules apply solely to costume prop weaponry. Our convention does not permit any real weapons to be used or brought to the convention at all as per our general policies above; violation of this rule will require immediate reporting to proper authorities.
Due to our proximity to the Ontario International Airport, we ask that you properly cover up or place costume-related prop weapons in bags when not in convention areas or on convention property.
Do you have a cosplay photo session, and you want to undo the peacebonding for that time period? W e have a great solution for you! We’ve got Ops Cosplay Liaison people out there wearing bright yellow CON OPS vests or a bright yellow CON OPS armband. They’ll be more than happy to remove any peacebonding for photos, but be sure to either flag them down again when you’re done to re-peacebond your props or return to the Ops office for re-peacebonding.
Privacy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.animelosangeles.org. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new announcements or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address (info@animelosangeles.org) given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only those who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, mailings or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Signage
Signage Approval Policy
Please be aware that no signs or other materials may be posted on the walls in and around the convention, unless it is official signage produced by Animé Los Angeles or signage specifically approved by the convention. In addition, any official signs that have been written on or otherwise defaced will be removed by staff; please respect the convention and other attendees who need the information provided on said signs and do not vandalize them.
If you wish to post a sign at the convention, please look over these rules for attendee-produced signage:
1- Signs may not be used for advertisement for a dealer’s hall/artist alley table, a panel, an event, etc. (This means signs containing hints or clues for a ribbon game or a scavenger hunt or something along those lines are allowed, but one simply directing people to your website or room party is not.)
2- Only one sign may be posted by a particular individual/group.
3- Signs must be approved by the Communications director or the con chair before the convention and presented to them at the convention to be stamped before being posted. (Any signage posted without the approval stamp will be removed, even if you received an email approving it.)
4- To be approved, signs must be reasonably professional in appearance and of a reasonable size.
5- Requests for approval must be submitted before the publications deadline (November 17, 2018).
e-mail any requests or questions to: pubs@animelosangeles.org
Search for:
© Copyright Animé Los Angeles
- Created by anydev.com
